<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>David Ebreo</title>
    <link>https://arhyth.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on David Ebreo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 21:28:45 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://arhyth.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Lang Checklist</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/new-lang-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 21:28:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/new-lang-checklist/</guid>
      <description>So You&amp;rsquo;re Learning a New Language Primitive types Error Handling Dependency management Async and/or Concurrency Abstraction Tooling Testing  Great! You want to learn a new language. You&amp;rsquo;re bored at work and you realize you&amp;rsquo;re current workhorse is limiting, or the stack at your new gig uses this weird esoteric stuff with too many parentheses and you hope you could understand even just some part of it. Either way, you want to learn one as efficiently as possible coz you&amp;rsquo;ve got other stuff to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks We Love</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/talks-we-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 15:31:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/talks-we-love/</guid>
      <description>Fascinating, inspirational, or challenging, one way or another.
Bret Victor&amp;rsquo;s seminal talk Inventing on Principle   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiny Shiny</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/shiny-shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 14:31:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/shiny-shiny/</guid>
      <description>Developers are obsessed with tools. It&amp;rsquo;s our natural tendency. The capacity for toolmaking separates us from our less evolved counterparts in the biology tree &amp;ndash; the ability to build on top of the existing, to refine the crude. It&amp;rsquo;s only too easy to get too involved in the tools than in the &amp;ldquo;building up&amp;rdquo; that they should be used for.
This past year I&amp;rsquo;m glad to have reached a certain level of comfort with developer tooling that I was able to invest (I should say waste) my time learning other programming concepts, patterns and techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2018 Day 3</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/code/aoc-2018-day3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:11:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/code/aoc-2018-day3/</guid>
      <description>This solution turned out much longer and even more complicated than I had hoped it would. My solutions for previous days involved pipelines of Enum functions and I purposely avoided going that route as they looked less intelligible with every additional line of anonymous iteration. I had hoped writing around &amp;ldquo;names&amp;rdquo; ala OOP would lend to a shorter and far more readable code. BurntSushi&amp;rsquo;s elegant implementation in Rust seemed ideal. However, the clarity of having names to code around quickly diluted with writing custom type boilerplate and this also due to Elixir having no actual types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pass me them params</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/pass-me-them-params/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 17:41:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/pass-me-them-params/</guid>
      <description>Explicit is better than implicit.
Zen of Python
 Pass me them params In my previous job, writing scripts to automate some of the repetitive tasks got me back into the programming route which eventually led me to consider a career shift. To be honest, automating tasks was, at least upfront, more hard work than additional straight up keystrokes. And without guarantee that the time invested will return in any quality or amount of savings, especially for smaller tasks, it was a day&amp;rsquo;s work worth of risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>colophon</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/about/colophon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 06:28:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/about/colophon/</guid>
      <description>This website is a personal homepage.
The site is built with Hugo—a static site generator made with Go. The website source code is available on GitHub. It uses the cocoa theme. The posts are written in Markdown.
The primary font face is Open Sans and the monospace font face is Ubuntu Mono. The social icons are from the Ionicons font set. CSS classes for code syntax highlighting are inserted during compile-time by Hugo using Pygments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>