<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on David Ebreo</title>
    <link>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on David Ebreo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 06:42:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://arhyth.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome tech blogs</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/awesome-tech-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 22:22:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/awesome-tech-blogs/</guid>
      <description>Awesome technical blogs Writing down just recent ones from memory for now. This is a growing list.
Personal  Dan Luu&amp;rsquo;s blog Will Larson&amp;rsquo;s blog the morning paper by Adrian Colyer. ELI20 for technical papers StaffEng by Will Larson brandur.org I don&amp;rsquo;t know whose this is but it&amp;rsquo;s great Nelson Elhage&amp;rsquo;s blog Eugene Wei&amp;rsquo;s blog. for stuff on product/strategy High Scalability by Todd Hoff Simon Eskildsen&amp;rsquo;s blog  Corporate  Dropbox Stripe Shopify Uber  Specific articles  The Dark Resistance Invisible Asymptotes Shitlists Choose Boring Technology  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The case of the crash looping pod</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/the-case-of-the-crash-looping-pod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 19:26:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/the-case-of-the-crash-looping-pod/</guid>
      <description>The case of the crash looping pod A few weeks ago at work we launched a new microservice which I had the opportunity to solely implement. Aside from some deserialization issues (an external API dependency with inconsistently typed response fields), everything seemed to be OK. Then it wasn&amp;rsquo;t. Our alerting system in GCP (Google Cloud) was on fire only hours after we went live.
The pods were on a crash loop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multiple SSH Keys for Github</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/multiple-ssh-keys-for-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 21:58:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/multiple-ssh-keys-for-github/</guid>
      <description>Using multiple SSH keys for Github   Create separate SSH keys and add them to appropriate Github account settings. Make sure they are easily distinguishable from each other.
  Modify the ssh config file ( ~/.ssh/config) or create it if there isn&amp;rsquo;t one.
  # Personal GitHub account Host github.com HostName github.com User git AddKeysToAgent yes UseKeychain yes IdentityFile ~/.ssh/id_rsa # Work/other GitHub account Host workhub HostName github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Lang Checklist</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/new-lang-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 21:28:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/new-lang-checklist/</guid>
      <description>New Language Checklist  Primitive types Error Handling Dependency management Async and/or Concurrency Abstraction Tooling Testing  Great! You want to learn a new language. You&amp;rsquo;re bored at work and you realize you&amp;rsquo;re current workhorse is limiting, or the stack at your new gig uses this weird esoteric stuff with too many parentheses and you hope you could understand even just some part of it. Either way, you want to learn one as efficiently as possible coz you&amp;rsquo;ve got other stuff to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks We Love</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/talks-we-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 15:31:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/talks-we-love/</guid>
      <description>Fascinating, inspirational, or challenging, one way or another.
Bret Victor&amp;rsquo;s seminal talk Inventing on Principle   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiny Shiny</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/shiny-shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 14:31:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/shiny-shiny/</guid>
      <description>Developers are obsessed with tools. It&amp;rsquo;s our natural tendency. The capacity for toolmaking separates us from our less evolved counterparts in the biology tree &amp;ndash; the ability to build on top of the existing, to refine the crude. It&amp;rsquo;s only too easy to get too involved in the tools than in the &amp;ldquo;building up&amp;rdquo; that they should be used for.
This past year I&amp;rsquo;m glad to have reached a certain level of comfort with developer tooling that I was able to invest (I should say waste) my time learning other programming concepts, patterns and techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pass me them params</title>
      <link>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/pass-me-them-params/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 17:41:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arhyth.github.io/blog/pass-me-them-params/</guid>
      <description>Explicit is better than implicit.
  Zen of Python
 Pass me them params In my previous job, writing scripts to automate some of the repetitive tasks got me back into the programming route which eventually led me to consider a career shift. To be honest, automating tasks was, at least upfront, more hard work than additional straight up keystrokes. And without guarantee that the time invested will return in any quality or amount of savings, especially for smaller tasks, it was a day&amp;rsquo;s work worth of risk.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>